constitutioncenter.org 2019-08-19

# Terms of of Use and Privacy Policy - National Constitution Center

**Disclaimers**

The National Constitution Center is an independent, nonprofit, nonpartisan organization. The materials on this site are offered to enhance your understanding of the Constitution and its role in our lives. Information is presented for educational and informational purposes.

The content provided on this website is not legal advice. You may contact us with general questions at [editor@constitutioncenter.org](mailto:editor@constitutioncenter.org).

Throughout this website, the National Constitution Center (“NCC”) provides links to outside resources and third-party websites. Unless specifically noted, the National Constitution Center disclaims any legal affiliation or agency relationship with third parties to whom we link or who link to our website. The National Constitution Center does not endorse, control, nor is it responsible for, the availability or content of these external sites.

By accessing, browsing, registering for an account, or by agreeing to the Terms of Use for this website (constitutioncenter.org, “Site”) or any mobile applications, and other products and services owned, controlled, operated, or hosted (whether now or in the future) by the National Constitution Center (collectively, “Services”) including but not limited to constitutioncenter.org, and all related applications and services, you accept and agree to be bound to these Terms of Use (“Terms”).  If you do not agree, do not use this Site. We reserve the right to amend these Terms at any time by posting the amended Terms on our Site. Your continued use of the site after any such amendments shall constitute your agreement to any revised terms.

**Using This Site**

You may only use this Site for lawful purposes in accordance with these Terms of Use.  You agree not to use this Site:

  * In any way that violates any federal, state, local or international law or regulation.
  * To transmit, or procure the sending of, any advertising or promotional material, including any “junk mail”, “chain letter” or “spam” or any other similar solicitation.

Additionally, you agree not to:

  * Use this Site in any manner that could disable, overburden, damage, or impair the Site or interfere with any other party’s use of the Site.
  * Use any robot, spider or other automatic device, process or means to access this Site for any purpose, including monitoring or copying any of the material.
  * Use any manual process to monitor or copy any of the material on this Site or for any other unauthorized purpose without our prior written consent (see Authorized Use, above).
  * Use any device, software or routine that interferes with the proper working of this Site.
  * Introduce any viruses or other material that is malicious or technologically harmful.
  * Attempt to gain unauthorized access to, interfere with, damage or disrupt any parts of this Site or the server on which this Site is stored.
  * Attack this Site via a denial-of-service attack or a distributed denial-of-service attack.
  * Otherwise attempt to interfere with the proper working of this Site.

**Right To Use Licensed Educational Content**

Licensed Educational Content. On its Site, the NCC provides educational text, videos, images and related supplementary materials that are owned by the NCC or third-party licensors (“Licensed Educational Content”).  The NCC grants to you a non-exclusive, non-transferable right to access and use the Licensed Educational Content made available on the NCC site solely for educational non-commercial purposes. Unless expressly indicated on the Website that a particular item of Licensed Educational Content is made available to you under alternate license terms, you may not sell or lease the Licensed Educational Content or use it for any other commercial purpose.  Unless otherwise expressly identified on the Website with respect to a particular item, all Licensed Educational Content is provided to the Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-No Derivatives 4.0 United States License (“CC BY-NC-ND 4.0”  available at <https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/>”). 

You are free to, share, copy and redistribute NCC’s Licensed Educational Content if you adhere to the following terms:

  * Attribution — You must give appropriate credit, identifying the NCC as the source of the Licensed Educational Content.
  * NonCommercial — You may not use the material for commercial purposes.
  * No Derivatives — If you remix, transform, or build upon the material, you may not distribute the modified material.

By using, downloading, or otherwise accessing such Licensed Educational Content, you agree to comply fully with all the terms and conditions of such Alternate License.

**Digital Millennium Copyright Act Notice Procedure**

_Notification of Infringement_

It is our policy to respond to clear notices of alleged copyright infringement. This page explains the information that must be included in these notices, as required by the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”). Upon receipt of a DMCA compliant notice, the NCC will expeditiously remove or disable access to the content that is the subject of the notice.

If you are a copyright owner or an authorized agent thereof, and you wish to file a notice of infringement with us, then you may submit a notice by providing the NCC’s Designated Copyright Agent with the following information in writing (please consult your legal counsel or see 17 U.S.C. Section 512(c)(3) to confirm these requirements):

  * A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
  * Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed.
  * Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit the NCC to locate the material on the NCC Site.
  * Information reasonably sufficient to permit the NCC to contact you, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an email address at which you may be contacted.
  * A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.
  * A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

Please note that under Section 512(f) of the DMCA, any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability. If you are unsure whether the material available online infringes your copyright, we suggest that you contact an attorney before sending us a notice.

_Counter-Notification_

The administrator of an affected site or the provider of affected content may make a counter notification under Sections 512(g)(2) and (3) of the DMCA. If you elect to send the NCC a counter notice, to be effective it must be a written communication that includes the following (please consult your legal counsel or see 17 U.S.C. Section 512(g)(3) to confirm these requirements):

  * A physical or electronic signature of the subscriber.
  * Identification of the material that has been removed or to which access has been disabled and the location at which the material appeared before it was removed or access to it was disabled.
  * A statement under penalty of perjury that the subscriber has a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or misidentification of the material to be removed or disabled.
  * The subscriber’s name, address, and telephone number, and a statement that the subscriber consents to the jurisdiction of Federal District Court for the judicial district in which the address is located, or if the subscriber’s address is outside of the United States, for any judicial district in which the NCC may be found, and that the subscriber will accept service of process from the person who provided notification under subsection (c)(1)(C) or an agent of such person.

Please note that under Section 512(f) of the Copyright Act, any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity was removed or disabled by mistake or misidentification may be subject to liability.

_Designated Copyright Agent_

The NCC’s Designated Copyright Agent to receive notifications and counter-notifications of claimed infringement can be reached as follows:

By mail:

Scott Bomboy  
Editor in Chief  
National Constitution Center  
525 Arch Street  
Philadelphia, PA 19106

By email:  
By telephone: (215) 409-6635

You acknowledge that if you fail to comply with all of the requirements of this section, your DMCA notice may not be valid.

**Trademark Policy**

The National Constitution Center owns multiple service marks and trademarks including but not limited to “America’s Town Hall,” “The National Constitution Center,” “NCC,” “Philadelphia Liberty Medal,” and the National Constitution Center Flag Logo (collectively the “NCC Trademarks”). 

All abbreviated reference to the National Constitution Center should be made to the “NCC.”

The National Constitution Center’s nonpartisan mission is to serve the nation and the world as a museum, a national headquarters for Civic Education, and a public forum for constitutional conversations. Towards these ends, the NCC provides live programs with leading historians, artists, and scholars, excellent educational content and exhibits in order to increase awareness and understanding of the U.S. Constitution.  Nonpartisanship is central to the NCC mission. The NCC seeks to inspire active citizenship by celebrating the American constitutional tradition for all citizens. To protect our nonpartisan mission, the NCC permits the NCC Trademarks to be used only in connection with approved nonpartisan educational events, exhibits, and content.

While you are encouraged to use the NCC’s educational content for all the purposes permitted by the Terms of Use on the NCC Site, you may not use the NCC Trademarks without the NCC’s prior written permission for any other purpose.

The names and trademarks of third parties may also appear on the NCC Website from time to time; you may not use these names and trademarks without prior, written permission of their respective owners.

Google Play and the Google Play logo are trademarks of Google Inc. The Apple logo, iPhone, iPod touch, and iTunes are trademarks of Apple Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries.

**Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting The National Constitution Center (“NCC”) website and reviewing our Privacy Policy. The NCC is committed to safeguarding the privacy and security of all our visitors. We want you to know how we use and protect the important information you provide to us. Our privacy and security practices are explained in detail below.

Unless you tell us otherwise, we shall assume that by using the NCC website or submitting your information to the NCC, you consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

**1\. Purpose of Collecting Information on our Website**

The NCC collects information as a way to further our mission as the only institution in America chartered by Congress to disseminate information about the United States Constitution on a nonpartisan basis.

When you visit the NCC website, we automatically collect and store information about your visit so that we can track and use it to make improvements to our site, improve website management and better fulfill our mission as both a museum and education outreach center. The information we collect includes:

  * The Internet Protocol (“IP”) address from which you access our site;
  * The name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, gmail.com, if you are connecting from a Google account);
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our website;
  * The date and time you access our site;
  * The pages, files, documents, videos and links that you view; and
  * The domain of the website which referred you linked to our website (the last website you visited before visiting the NCC site).

This information is stored for NCC use only. Access to your personal information is limited to personnel who need access for NCC purposes.

**2.  ** **Cookies and Pixel Tags**

The NCC website may use technologies such as “cookies” and “pixel tags” to improve our website and your experience.

“Cookies” are small data files that are automatically sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can enable us to remember what items are in your shopping cart, and personalize your experience. You may choose to set your browser so that it does not accept cookies.

“Pixel tags” are tiny graphical images embedded in emails or webpages. Pixel tags are used to determine what parts of a website a visitor has viewed, or whether an email was successfully opened. These technologies do not contain any personal information about you. They are used to gather information to analyze traffic to our website, improve our content and navigation, enhance our marketing efforts, personalize your experience, and provide information tailored to your interests based on your online behavior.

The NCC works with third-party analytics and marketing partners who use technologies such as cookies and pixel tags on our behalf.

**3.  ** **Email Communication**

The NCC sends email to its members, donors and visitors to its website. Email recipients may opt out at any time by following the “unsubscribe” instructions included in the email message.

**4\. Sharing Your Personal Information**

If you send us personal information – by submitting an email, completing an online form or survey, requesting materials or information, ordering merchandise or museum tickets, donating to support the important work of the NCC or signing up for membership – we will use this information to respond to your inquiry or request. Additionally, if you have checked the “Please add my name to your mailing list” box, we will add your name, email and mailing address to our mailing list database.

We use outside vendors to provide certain services, such as companies that process credit card transactions or analyze the traffic on our site. We permit these independent vendors access to the information they need to perform their functions, but they are not permitted to use your information for any other purpose.

We do not normally distribute visitors’ names, email addresses or other identifying information submitted through this site with any third party. Such information is never sold or rented to a third party. We do, however, occasionally trade this information with other charitable or educational organizations whose services or products might interest you, but whose privacy policies may differ from ours. If you prefer not to have your information shared with other organizations, you may uncheck the “Allow the NCC to share my name with other organizations” box on any form or email that you submit to the NCC.

You may contact us at [editor@constitutioncenter.org](mailto:editor@constitutioncenter.org) for a current list of organizations with whom we trade information.

If you have questions about how this policy applies to your information, or if you would like the NCC to delete or change any information you provided to us, please contact us at [editor@constitutioncenter.org](mailto:editor@constitutioncenter.org).

**5\. Children’s Privacy on the Web**

The National Constitution Center takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from children under thirteen years of age.

If you are a parent or guardian, we encourage you to become involved in your children's online experience, and to share your knowledge and experience with your young learners. If you are under 13, please do not provide us with any contact or other information, including your name, address or email address. If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, please obtain permission from your parent or guardian before registering or sending any contact or other information to the NCC.

Parents may contact us at [editor@constitutioncenter.org](mailto:editor@constitutioncenter.org) to update or delete any of their children's personal information.

**6\. Purchasing Advance Tickets and Web Ticketing Services**

The NCC provides visitors with the opportunity to purchase advance tickets online. This service is provided by VISTA TICKETING/museumtix.com. When a visitor to the NCC website chooses to reserve tickets online, they are linked to the museumtix.com site. Visitors to the museumtix.com site are subject to that site’s privacy policies. Please refer to the museumtix.com site for more information.

**7\. Other Online Purchases**

The NCC also provides visitors with an opportunity to make online purchases from the museum’s retail store as well as purchase a museum membership or make a contribution to our organization through an online donation/membership page. When visitors to our website choose to make an online purchase, they are linked to a website served by Aramark. Similarly, when website visitors choose to purchase a membership or make a donation to the NCC, they are linked to a website served by Blackbaud. Visitors to the Aramark and Blackbaud website are subject to those sites’ privacy policies and should refer to <https://www.aramark.com/other/privacy-policy> and <https://www.blackbaud.com/company/privacy-policy/north-america> for further information.

**8\. Security**

Access to your information is limited to personnel who need access for NCC purposes. All online transactions conducted on our website are protected by industry-approved encryption techniques in the gathering, storage and transfer of financial data.

**9\. Donors, Supporters and Volunteers**

The NCC collects information from our donors, volunteers, and supporters, both online and offline, including information collected thorough our Website, mobile applications, and social media, as well as any other electronic, written, or oral communications.

The NCC understands that philanthropy merits your respect and trust. To this end, all NCC donors are entitled to information about the organization’s mission, the way the organization intends to use donated resources, and its capacity to use donations effectively for their intended purposes. The NCC also assures that information about donations will be handled with respect and with confidentiality to the extent provided by law.

The NCC collects and maintains donor information that is voluntarily provided to us, such as:

  * Contact information such as name, address, telephone number and e-mail address
  * Gift giving information (including payment information)
  * Information on events attended, publications received and special requests for information related to the NCC or its programs
  * Information provided in the form of comments and suggestions

The NCC uses this information to provide our donors, volunteers, and supporters with better service and with information about the NCC’s events and support or volunteer opportunities. Payment information is used only for donation or payment processing and is not retained for other purposes.

The NCC will not sell, rent, or lease your information to other organizations. We occasionally share portions of our member lists with other non-profit organizations, which do the same for us, in an effort to help the NCC grow. To opt out, please contact NCC Membership at 215-409-6767 or [membership@constitutioncenter.org](http://membership@constitutioncenter.org/).

**10\. Updating Your Information and Contacting Us with Questions**

The NCC will discontinue or change the method used to contact any person, including donors, volunteers, and supporters, as soon as possible upon that person’s written request.

_General Privacy Inquiries._   If you have general questions about how this policy applies to your information, or if you would like the NCC to delete or change any information you provided to us, please contact us by email at [editor@constitutioncenter.org](mailto:editor@constitutioncenter.org) or write us at:

National Constitution Center  
Attention:  Privacy Officer  
Independence Mall  
525 Arch Street  
Philadelphia, PA 19106-1595

_Donor Inquiries_. If you have questions about this policy applies to you as a donor or would like us to change or delete donor information you provided to us, please contact our Senior Director of Development Rebecca Bolden by email at [rbolden@constitutioncenter.org](mailto:%20rbolden@constitutioncenter.org) or write us at:

National Constitution Center  
Attention:  Development  
Independence Mall  
525 Arch Street  
Philadelphia, PA 19106-1595

You can also contact [membership@constitutioncenter.org](mailto:membership@constitutioncenter.org). 

**11\. Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

Any changes we make to this Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page.

Last modified: June 6, 2019
